openmp.org 2019-05-02

# OpenMP ARB Privacy Policy - OpenMP

Your privacy is very important to the OpenMP Architecture Review Board (ARB). Our goal is to treat your personal information with the utmost respect and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please review it for information about how personal information is collected and used on this site and at events you attend. By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Information collection and use**

The OpenMP ARB is the sole collector and owner of information collected on this website and at events. We will not use the collected personal  information other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

**What Information is collected and for what purposes**

We collect personal information only as necessary to allow you to participate in our programs and services, This personal information may include your name, email address, phone number, mobile number, affiliation, and physical address.

Your contact information may be used to send you invitations to our programs and events.

**International data processing**

For those of you who are residents of a European Union member state and subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) , your personal data may be transferred outside the European Union to the United States as necessary for us to process your personal data.  All personal data will be processed for lawful purposes as described in this Privacy Policy, including the legitimate interests of OpenMP ARB .

**Use of cookies**

The website uses cookies only as unique session identifiers or to identify you as an authorized user of the site (if you access secured areas of the site, such as the Discussion Forums). If you disable cookies in your browser, use of this website may be limited.

**Sharing of information**

No personal information collected by the OpenMP.org website or at events is shared with any third party beyond the OpenMP ARB and its members.

**Linked sites**

The OpenMP.org website may contain links to other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.

**Modifications to our Privacy Policy**

The OpenMP Architecture Review Board reserves the right to modify or supplement this Privacy Policy statement at any time. If we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will update this website to include such change. If at any time the OpenMP ARB decides to use personal information collected in a manner or for a purpose other than those stated at the time such information was collected, we will notify you by email. You will have a choice as to whether this information will be used in that manner or for those purposes.

**Contacting us regarding this policy**

In order to continually monitor and strengthen our privacy procedure, we can be [contacted here](https://www.openmp.org/about/contact-us/) if you have questions about privacy that were not answered here. We welcome any suggestions.

###### Revised June 2018
